Guide to the American political campaigns miscellany, 1868-2016
American political campaigns miscellany
- Series V. Buttons
  - Kennedy Presidential Campaign, 1992; 6477.BT0274; Items: 2 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Kennedy, Ted
  - King Attorney General Campaign, 6477.BT0275; Items: 1 (Box 25)
  - Koch Mayor Campaign, 6477.BT0276; Items: (Box 25)
  - Krupsak, 6477.BT0278; Items: 1 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Krupsak, Carey
  - Landon/Knox Presidential Campaign, 6477.BT0282; Items: 1 (Box 25)
  - Lauder for Mayor Campaign, 6477.BT0279; Items: 1 (Box 25)
  - Lefkowitz Attorney General Campaign, 6477.BT0280; Items: 2 (Box 25)
  - Lester State Senate Campaign, 6477.BT0281; Items: 1 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Lester, Jack
  - Levitt for Congress Campaign, 6477.BT0283; Items: 1 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Levitt, John
  - Lindsay Presidential Campaign, 1972; 6477.BT0284; Items: 4 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Lindsay, John
  - Macchiarola for Comptroller Campaign, 1989; 6477.BT0286; Items: 1 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Macchiarola, Frank
  - Maltese for Senate, Congress Campaigns, 1984 and; 6477.BT0285; Items: (Box 25)
    Candidate: Maltese, Serphin
  - Manton for Congress Campaign, 6477.BT0287; Items: 1 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Manton, Tom
  - Mason for Assembly Campaign, 6477.BT0288; Items: 1 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Mason, Trudy
  - McBride Presidential Campaign, 1976; 6477.BT0289; Items: 1 (Box 25)
    Candidate: McBride
  - McCain Presidential Campaign, 2000; 6477.BT0290; Items: 1 (Box 25)
    Candidate: McCain, John
  - McCarthy Presidential Campaign, 6477.BT0291; Items: 1 (Box 25)
  - McGovern/Shriver, McGovern/Eagleton Presidential Campaigns, 1972 and; 6477.BT0292; Items: 6 (Box 25)
    Candidate: McGovern, George
  - McMillan Campaign for Senate, 6477.BT0293; Items: 1 (Box 25)
  - Messinger Campaign for Borough President, 6477.BT0294; Items: 1 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Messinger, Ruth
  - Moore Campaign for Alderman, 6477.BT0295; Items: 1 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Moore, Joe
  - Mondale/Ferraro Presidential Campaign, 1984; 6477.BT0296; Items: 6 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Mondale, Walter and Ferraro, Geraldine
  - Moynihan Campaign for Senator, 6477.BT0297; Items: (Box 25)
  - Nixon/Lodge and Nixon Presidential Campaign, and 1992; 6477.BT0298; Items: 7 (Box 25)
    Election: and 1992
    Party: Republcan
  - Nixon/Agnew Presidential Campaign, 1968; 6477.BT0299; Items: 10 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Nixon, Richard and Agnew
  - Nunn Campaigns for President and Senate, 1992 and; 6477.BT0300; Items: 2 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Nunn, Sam
  - O'Rourke/Kavanagh Campaign for Governor, 6477.BT0301; Items: 1 (Box 25)
    Candidate: O'Rourke, Andy and Kavanagh, Mike
  - Paul Presidential Campaign, 6477.BT0302; Items: 1 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Paul, Ron
  - Perot Presidential Campaign, 1992; 6477.BT0303; Items: 2 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Perot
  - Quayle Campaigns, 6477.BT0304; Items: 2 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Quayle, Dan
  - Rabbitt Presidential Campaign, 1988; 6477.BT0305; Items: 1 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Rabbitt
  - Ravitch Campaign for Mayor, 6477.BT0306; Items: 1 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Ravitch
  - Ravitz Campaign for Assembly, 6477.BT0307; Items: 1 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Ravitz
  - Rawson Campaign for Assembly, 6477.BT0308; Items: 1 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Rawson, Angela
  - Reiter Campaign for Congress, 6477.BT0309; Items: 1 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Reiter, Fran
  - Robb Presidential Campaign, 1992; 6477.BT0310; Items: 2 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Robb, Chuck
  - Reagan/Bush Presidential Campaign, 1976, 1980, 1984; 6477.BT0311; Items: 22 (Box 25)
    Election: 1976, 1980 and 1984
  - Regan Campaign for State Comptroller, 6477.BT0312; Items: 3 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Regan, Ned
  - Robertson Presidential Campaign, 1988; 6477.BT0313; Items: 2 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Robertson, Pat
  - Rockefeller/Javits Presidential Campaign, 6477.BT0314; Items: 4 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Rockefeller, Javits
  - Roosevelt Presidential Campaign, 6477.BT0315; Items: 5 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Roosevelt, Franklin D.
  - Ross Presidential Campaign, 1992; 6477.BT0316; Items: 1 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Ross
  - Schroeder Presidential Campaign, 6477.BT0317; Items: 1 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Schroeder
  - Shulman Campaign for Borough President, 6477.BT0318; Items: 1 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Shulman, Claire
  - Simon Presidential Campaign, 1988; 6477.BT0319; Items: 2 (Box 25)
  - Solomon Campaign for Congress, 6477.BT0320; Items: 1 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Solomon
  - Stein Campaign for Congress, 6477.BT0321; Items: 3 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Stein, Andrew
  - Stevenson Presidential Campaign, 6477.BT0322; Items: 3 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Stevenson, Adlai
  - Taft Presidential Campaign, 6477.BT0323; Items: 1 (Box 25)
  - Truman Memorial Button, 1984; 6477.BT0324; Items: 1 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Truman, Harry S.
  - Tongas Presidential Campaign, 1992; 6477.BT0325; Items: 2 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Tsongas
  - Udall Presidential Campaign, 6477.BT0326; Items: 1 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Udall
  - Wagner Presidential Campaign, 6477.BT0327; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Wagner
  - Wallace Presidential Campaign, 1968; 6477.BT0328; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Wallace
  - Warren/Mickells Presidential Campaign, 1988; 6477.BT0329; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Warren, James and Mickells, Kathleen
  - Weiss Campaign for Congress, 6477.BT0330; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Weiss, Ted
  - Wes Presidential Campaign, 6477.BT0331; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Wes
  - Wilder Presidential Campaign, 6477.BT0332; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Wilder, Doug
  - Williams Presidential Campaign, 1992; 6477.BT0333; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Williams, Walter
  - Willkie/McNary Presidential Campaign, 6477.BT0334; Items: 4 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Willkie
  - Wilson Presidential Campaign, 6477.BT0335; Items: 1 (Box 26)
  - Wyche Campaign for Senate, 1986; 6477.BT0336; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Wyche
  - Democratic Convention Buttons, 1992; 6477.BT0337; Items: 4 (Box 26)
  - Vote Republican Buttons, 6477.BT0338; Items: 2 (Box 26)
  - Medic Pins, 1919, 1936; 6477.BT0339; Items: 2 (Box 26)
  - Anti-War buttons, 6477.BT0340; Items: 6 (Box 26)
  - Miscellaneous Political Statement Buttons, 6477.BT0341; Items: 14 (Box 26)
  - Miscellaneous Buttons, 6477.BT0342; Items: 11 (Box 26)
  - Various Candidate buttons, 6477.BT0343; Items: 29 (Box 26)
  - Various Candidate buttons, 6477.BT0344; Items: 10 (Box 27)
- Series VI. Cartoons
  - Reprints of Four Bobby Kennedy Political Cartoons, 1964; 6477.CA0001; Items: 2 (Box 19)
    Candidate: Kennedy, Robert
  - Human Relations (Photocopy of Jules Feiffer Cartoon), 1968; 6477.CA0002; Items: 1 (Box 19)
  - It'll Be Good To Have You Back, ca. 1980; 6477.CA0003; Items: 1 (Box 19)
  - One Tiny Reason to Vote For Reagan, ca. 1980; 6477.CA0004; Items: 1 (Box 19)
- Series VII. Maps & Charts
  - Presidential Election Map, 1964; 6477.MC0001; Items: 1 (Box 19)
- Series VIII. Pamphlets
  - The McGovern Encyclopedia, ca. 1972; 6477.PA0001; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
  - People Want Someone Out Among Them, 1972; 6477.PA0002; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
    Candidate: Schamel, John B.
  - "Jimmy's Breakthrough" Time Magazine Cover, Jimmy Carter, 1976; 6477.PA0003; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - "Ford Closes In" Time Magazine Cover, Gerald Ford, 1976; 6477.PA0004; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - "Man of the Year" Time Magazine, Ronald Reagan, 1981; 6477.PA0005; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Official Inaugural Program January 20, 1937, 1937; 6477.PA0006; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Presidential Inauguration 1953, 1953; 6477.PA0007; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - "Presidential Elections of the 20th Century" Portfolio by The New York Times, 1968; 6477.PA0008; Items: 19 (Box 17)
    Party: Republican; Democratic
  - 1967 Catalog of Republican Campaign Materials, 1967; 6477.PA0009; Items: 3 (Box 10)
  - George McGovern Speaks On The Issues, ca. 1972; 6477.PA0010; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - The Clearest Choice Of The Century, ca. 1972; 6477.PA0011; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Facts For Voters, 1972; 6477.PA0012; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Presidential Handbook '72, 1972; 6477.PA0013; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - The Citizen's Choice Humphrey Or Nixon By Nelson W. Polsby, ca. 1968; 6477.PA0014; Items: 1 (Box 10)
    Candidate: Humphrey, Hubert H.; Nixon, Richard M.
  - McGovern Works for Us..., ca. 1972; 6477.PA0015; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - The College Republican, 1972; 6477.PA0016; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Young Voters For The President, ca. 1972; 6477.PA0017; Items: 2 (Box 10)
  - Young Voters For The President Press Kit, ca. 1972; 6477.PA0018; Items: 3 (Box 10)
  - The Wallace Stand. Vol. 1, no's 1-3, Vol.2, no.1, 1971; 1972; 6477.PA0019; Items: 4 (Box 10)
  - McGovern The Time Is Now, ca. 1972; 6477.PA0020; Items: 1 (Box 17)
  - Robison Seeks Big Win in New 27th Congressional District, ca. 1972; 6477.PA0021; Items: 1 (Box 17)
  - "This is George Romney, Republican", ca. 1968; 6477.PA0022; Items: 1 (Box 10)
    Candidate: Romney, George
  - "Crime, Reform & the Voter"by Elmo Roper and Louis Harris, 1951; 6477.PA0023; Items: 1 (Box 9)
  - Military Appropriations Fiscal 1948-Fiscal 1953, ca.1953; 6477.PA0024; Items: 1 (Box 9)
  - "Please Help Our Poor American Cousins...", 1952; 6477.PA0025; Items: 1 (Box 9)
  - "Are We Being Talked Into War?" by Corliss Lamont, ca. 1952; 6477.PA0026; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - "Effects of American Foreign Policy" by Corliss Lamont, ca. 1952; 6477.PA0027; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - "Soviet Aggression: Myth Or Reality?" by Corliss Lamont, ca. 1952; 6477.PA0028; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - "The Other Evil" by Vito Marcantonio, 1952; 6477.PA0029; Items: 1 (Box 10)
    Candidate: Hallinan, Vincent
  - "Only One Candidate For U.S. Senator Says It...", ca. 1952; 6477.PA0030; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Veterans For Stevenson, ca. 1952; 6477.PA0031; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - "Let's Talk Sense To The American People", ca. 1952; 6477.PA0032; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - The Record Of Adlai E. Stevenson In Illinois, ca. 1952; 6477.PA0033; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - It's Up To You Now Vote, ca. 1952; 6477.PA0034; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Questions and Answers Debunking the Bunk, ca. 1952; 6477.PA0035; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Stevenson Speaks!, ca. 1952; 6477.PA0036; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Adlai E. Stevenson of Illinois, ca. 1952; 6477.PA0037; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Fact Sheet Volunteers for Stevenson If the Republicans Win..., ca. 1952; 6477.PA0038; Items: 1 (Box 9)
  - Stevenson Special Issue 1 Put Out By Students For Stevenson, 1952; 6477.PA0039; Items: 1 (Box 9)
  - Agricultural Progress News Letter October 1952, 1952; 6477.PA0040; Items: 1 (Box 9)
  - "Adlai Stevenson The Man And His Views...", 1952; 6477.PA0041; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Fact Sheet Civil Rights, ca. 1952; 6477.PA0042; Items: 1 (Box 9)
  - An Address By Governor Adlai E. Stevenson Chicago, Ill., 1952; 6477.PA0043; Items: 1 (Box 9)
  - Text of Speech By Governor Stevenson In Cleveland..., 1952; 6477.PA0044; Items: 1 (Box 9)
  - Text of Speech By Governor Stevenson At Madison Square Garden..., 1952; 6477.PA0045; Items: 1 (Box 9)
  - Excerpts From The Address By Governor Stevenson...Tampa Florida..., 1952; 6477.PA0046; Items: 1 (Box 9)
  - Excerpts From Public Statements of Adlai E. Stevenson..., 1952; 6477.PA0047; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - The Negro Choice For President, ca. 1952; 6477.PA0048; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Win with Stevenson The Champion Of Civil Rights, ca. 1952; 6477.PA0049; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - A Man Named Stevenson, ca. 1952; 6477.PA0050; Items: 2 (Box 10)
  - Let's Hear Them Answer These, ca. 1952; 6477.PA0051; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Up On The Farm, ca. 1952; 6477.PA0052; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - How's Business?, ca. 1952; 6477.PA0053; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - On The Job 61,000,000 Of Us!, ca. 1952; 6477.PA0054; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Let's Measure It!, ca. 1952; 6477.PA0055; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Meet The Candidates: Adlai E. Stevenson..., ca. 1952; 6477.PA0056; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Invest Five Minutes in Comparing..., ca. 1952; 6477.PA0057; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Time For A Change? Bill Gets The Facts (Comic Book Format), ca. 1952; 6477.PA0058; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - The Democrat Vol. 2 Washington D.C. October 4, 1952, 1952; 6477.PA0059; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - The Record: Special Election Edition October 1952, 1952; 6477.PA0060; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Compare The General Governor Stevenson You Be The Judge, ca. 1952; 6477.PA0061; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - O'Connor for Congress Committee Newsletter, ca. 1952; 6477.PA0062; Items: 1 (Box 10)
    Candidate: O'Connor, Donald
  - If You Live In The 36th Congressional District-You Are Here, ca. 1952; 6477.PA0063; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Vote Row "B" Keep Winning With A Real Liberal, ca. 1952; 6477.PA0064; Items: 1 (Box 10)
    Candidate: Cashmore, John
  - The National Voter September 1 1952...Summary of ...Platforms, 1952; 6477.PA0065; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - An Open Letter To American Farmers, 1952; 6477.PA0066; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - If You Want A Real Job Of Government House Cleaning..., ca. 1952; 6477.PA0067; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Young America Listen:, ca. 1952; 6477.PA0068; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Ike The Man You Can Trust To..., ca. 1952; 6477.PA0069; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - 7 Reasons Why You And Every Veteran Should Vote For Ike, Nixon And Ives, ca. 1952; 6477.PA0070; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Ives: Why You Need To Keep This Man In The U.S. Senate..., ca. 1952; 6477.PA0071; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - The Case For A Republican Congress, 1952; 6477.PA0072; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Our Foreign Policy Crisis A Tribute To Gen. Douglas MacArthur..., 1951; 6477.PA0073; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Prosperity? Security?...(Anti-Democratic), ca. 1952; 6477.PA0074; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Americans For Democratic Action (Anti ADA), 1950; 6477.PA0075; Items: 1 (Box 9)
  - A Raid On the People's Pocketbook Speech Of Hon. Daniel A. Reed..., 1951; 6477.PA0076; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - The People of New York State Back Ike!, ca. 1952; 6477.PA0077; Items: 1 (Box 9)
  - "A Republican Landslide..." (Front Page of So.Cayuga Tribune...Nov. 6, 1952), 1952; 6477.PA0078; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - The New America (Newspaper, Vol 1, Numbers 2-5, October 1956), 1956; 6477.PA0079; Items: 4 (Box 10)
  - Democratic Digest February 1957, 1957; 6477.PA0080; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Campaign Facts Nineteen Fifty-Six, 1956; 6477.PA0081; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Dollars and Sense Here's What Ike Put In Your Wallet!, 1956; 6477.PA0082; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Pocket Reminter Acheivements of the Eisenhower-Nixon Administration..., ca. 1956; 6477.PA0083; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - The Truth About Nixon, ca. 1956; 6477.PA0084; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Who Is Blocking The Eisenhower Labor Program, 1956; 6477.PA0085; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Forward With Eisenhower-Nixon (Comic Book Format), 1956; 6477.PA0086; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - This Is The Man..., ca. 1956; 6477.PA0087; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - 7 Reasons Why You And Every Veteran Should Vote For Ike, Dick And Jack, ca. 1956; 6477.PA0088; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - The Republican Record '53 To '56 Eisenhower-Nixon Accomplishments..., 1956; 6477.PA0089; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Our Partnership In Creating A World Of Peace...Address by...Nixon, 1956; 6477.PA0090; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Dear Citizen For Eisenhower..., 1956; 6477.PA0091; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Elect Jacob K. Javits A Fighting United States Senator, 1956; 6477.PA0092; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Citizens For Javits; "Dear Colleagues...", 1956; 6477.PA0093; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Wagner Will Vote For You In The Senate, 1956; 6477.PA0094; Items: 1 (Box 10)
    Candidate: Wagner, Robert F.
  - The Candidates (Photographs of Stevenson and Kefauver), 1956; 6477.PA0095; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Ooops! What Am I Saying?, 1956; 6477.PA0096; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - The Issues, 1956; 6477.PA0097; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Come Back Tomorrow, Kids, 1956; 6477.PA0098; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - What Happened To That "Great Crusade"?, 1956; 6477.PA0099; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Your Candidate Adlai E. Stevenson, 1956; 6477.PA0100; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - The New Voter And The New America, 1956; 6477.PA0101; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Nixon?, 1956; 6477.PA0102; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - The Farmer Gets The "Business", 1956; 6477.PA0103; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - No Time For The Old People, 1956; 6477.PA0104; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - And They Say An Elephant Never Forgets, 1956; 6477.PA0105; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - But The Honeymoon Was Short!, 1956; 6477.PA0106; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - The Party For You Not Just The Few, 1956; 6477.PA0107; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - How The GOP Drives Small Business...Out Of Existence!, 1956; 6477.PA0108; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Which Party Is Young At Heart?, 1956; 6477.PA0109; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - The Ticket For You Adlai Stevenson, 1956; 6477.PA0110; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Keep The Tiger Out!! Boss Murphy And Tammany Hall..., n/a; 6477.PA0111; Items: 2 (Box 10)
  - $40,000,000 Back Taxes Collected Arrears Of Ten Years, 1910; 6477.PA0112; Items: 1 (Box 10)
    Candidate: O'Malley, Edward R.
    Election: 1910
  - Speech of Hon. Wm. Sulzer Of New York In The House Of Representatives..., 1904; 6477.PA0113; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Speeches of Hon. John Sharp Williams Of Missippi In the House..., 1904; 6477.PA0114; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Speech of Hon. Augustus O. Bacon of Georgia In the Senate..., 1904; 6477.PA0115; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Extracts From Speeches Of Hon. Claude Kitchin...In The House..., ca. 1904; 6477.PA0116; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Rome the Catholic Capital...ny William J. Bryan, n/a; 6477.PA0117; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Where Is The "Full Dinner Pail " Now?, 1908; 6477.PA0118; Items: (Box 10)
  - Shall The People Rule? Notification Speech Of William Jennings Bryan, 1908; 6477.PA0119; Items: 2 (Box 10)
  - The Trust Question, 1908; 6477.PA0120; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Guaranteed Banks, 1908; 6477.PA0121; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Labor Speech of William Jennings Bryan, 1908; 6477.PA0122; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Former Secretary Of State Olney...Tells Why Bryan Should Be Elected..., 1908; 6477.PA0123; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Mr. Bryan's answer To Van Cleave, 1908; 6477.PA0124; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Sherman's Record [by] H.R. Fuller, 1908; 6477.PA0125; Items: 1 (Box 10)
    Candidate: Sherman, James S.
    Party: Reca. 1908
  - Bryan's Standpunkt In Der Tarif-Frage, 1908; 6477.PA0126; Items: 2 (Box 10)
  - Die Campagne Fragen Im Lichte Der Barteigeschichte, ca. 1908; 6477.PA0127; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Why Dr. Eliot Will Vote For Wilson And Marshall, ca. 1912; 6477.PA0128; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - A Dozen Reasons, ca. 1912; 6477.PA0129; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - "Pass Prosperity Around" Speech Of Albert J. Beveridge, ca. 1912; 6477.PA0130; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Party Platforms Progressive Democratic Republican In Deadly Parallel, 1912; 6477.PA0131; Items: 2 (Box 10)
    Party: Progressive; Democratic; Republican
  - National Democratic Platform...1912, 1912; 6477.PA0132; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - A Pledge-Redeeming Party: Speech of Charles W. Fairbanks..., 1916; 6477.PA0133; Items: 1 (Box 10)
    Candidate: Fairbanks, Charles W.
  - Our Prosperity by Representative William E. Humphrey, ca. 1916; 6477.PA0134; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - The Hughes Pledge, 1916; 6477.PA0135; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Why Charles E. Hughes Should Be Elected..., 1916; 6477.PA0136; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Hughes And Wilson On Labor, ca. 1916; 6477.PA0137; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - The Life Story Of Charles E. Hughes, ca. 1916; 6477.PA0138; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Lest We Forget, 1916; 6477.PA0139; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - American First And American Efficient, 1916; 6477.PA0140; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - American Protection, 1916; 6477.PA0141; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Coercion Is Un-American, 1916; 6477.PA0142; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Address Of Charles E. Hughes Accepting The Republican Nomination..., 1916; 6477.PA0143; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Our Candidates: For President Charles Evans Hughes..., 1916; 6477.PA0144; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Achievements Of The Republican Party, 1916; 6477.PA0145; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Harveyisms 1913-1916, 1916; 6477.PA0146; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - "Molasses to Catch Flies" 25 Broken Platform Pledges..., 1916; 6477.PA0147; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - The Democratic Tariff Law, 1916; 6477.PA0148; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Campaign Catechism, 1916; 6477.PA0149; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Duty First: Speech of Theodore Roosevelt..., 1916; 6477.PA0150; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Words And Deeds: Speech of Theodore Roosevelt, 1916; 6477.PA0151; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - The Story Of Mexico By Senator Henry Cabot Lodge, 1916; 6477.PA0152; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Wilson's Record Should Make Every Progressive Vote For Hughes, 1916; 6477.PA0153; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Why I Shall Vote For Hughes Instead Of Wilson, 1916; 6477.PA0154; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Consent Of The Governed: How It Is Practiced By Democrats..., n/a; 6477.PA0155; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Bryan's Power For Doing Mischief, 1900; 6477.PA0156; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - The Achievements Of The Democratic Party And Its Leader, 1916; 6477.PA0157; Items: 3 (Box 10)
  - What Thomas A. Edison A Lifelong Republican Says, 1916; 6477.PA0158; Items: 2 (Box 10)
  - Dr. Charles W. Eliot Dean Of American Educators..., 1916; 6477.PA0159; Items: 2 (Box 10)
  - Labor's Charter Of Freedom, 1916; 6477.PA0160; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - "We Challenge All Comers" Achievement VS. Evasion, 1916; 6477.PA0161; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Do YOU Think The Glory Of America Would Be Enhanced By A War..., 1916; 6477.PA0162; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - If There Had Been No Woodrow Wilson President..., 1916; 6477.PA0163; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Record Of Hughes As An Enemy Of Labor, 1916; 6477.PA0164; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Henry Ford's Reasons For Supporting Wilson, 1916; 6477.PA0165; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Sixteen Million Voters Appeal For Light!, 1916; 6477.PA0166; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - "Yes!" Or "No!" Mr. Hughes?, 1916; 6477.PA0167; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - 10 Reasons Why You Should Vote For Woodrow Wilson, 1916; 6477.PA0168; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Germans Catspaws For Hughes, 1916; 6477.PA0169; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Hughes Alliance In The State Of New York, 1916; 6477.PA0170; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - National Hughes Alliance, 1916; 6477.PA0171; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Mr. Wilson As seen By One Of His Family Circle, 1916; 6477.PA0172; Items: 2 (Box 10)
  - To The Voter Who does His Own Thinking, ca. 1917; 6477.PA0173; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - As A Man Thinketh/The Female Of The Species, n/a; 6477.PA0174; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Suffrage Not A Natural Right, 1915; 6477.PA0175; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Why Female Suffrage Would Be Inexpedient, n/a; 6477.PA0176; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - The Remonstrance Against Woman Suffrage: Second Campaign Number, 1915; 6477.PA0177; Items: 2 (Box 9)
  - For County Clerk Vote For Edith A. Ellis, n/a; 6477.PA0178; Items: 1 (Box 10)
    Candidate: Ellis, Edith
  - Prohibition In Ithaca: What It Means To You, ca. 1915; 6477.PA0179; Items: 2 (Box 10)
  - The Iron Platform Extra No.XXVI, 1863; 6477.PA0180; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - The People And Not the Saloons To Rule New York, n/a; 6477.PA0181; Items: 2 (Box 10)
  - The Reform Bulletin Vol. 6, No.40, 1915; 6477.PA0182; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Will The People Of Tompkins County Allow The Liquor Traffic..., ca. 1915; 6477.PA0183; Items: 2 (Box 10)
  - State Of New York Tax Department (Changes in tax and other laws), 1915; 6477.PA0184; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Proposed Taxation Article For The New York Constitution, 1915; 6477.PA0185; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Letter To Elihu Root By Geo. W. Perkins...Against The Proposed Constitution, 1915; 6477.PA0186; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Representation The Wrong And The Right Way Of Electing Legislators, 1915; 6477.PA0187; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Help the Constitution, 1915; 6477.PA0188; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Vote Against The Proposed Constitution!, 1915; 6477.PA0189; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Constitution Making In New York, 1915; 6477.PA0190; Items: 1 (Box 9)
  - What Governor Glynn Has Done For New York's Farms, ca. 1914; 6477.PA0191; Items: 2 (Box 10)